[Music]
even during eras of sadness in my life
animals have always been a source of joy
and healing
the gentle wisdom and the demeanor of
these creatures make me feel safe
i always find it interesting how at our
lowest points it can be so hard to look
outside of ourselves and reach out to
others be it a human or another type of
animal
and yet that is so often where healing
begins
[Music]
i've had the pleasure of spending time
on a few different horse ranches
throughout my life
once i spent 10 days in saddle string
wyoming writing at dawn and dusk until
my backside was incredibly sore
since i was a little girl i've always
loved horses
something about their soft eyes their
power
and their history in the american west
has been alluring for as long as i can
remember while i don't think we'll ever
brag about it one thursday morning last
week my town of barely more than 500
people made national headlines
we had the worst air quality in the
entire nation
it's been an insane week and i really
wasn't sure what to share with you
because i didn't want this video to be
overly sad
i know so many people come to this
channel to escape the realities of daily
life
but as i was putting it together with my
brother i realized that if it ends up
being a bit sad then
i guess that's okay
sometimes things are sad and there's
very little to see that is positive
and yet even in that realization life
can be ever more poignant reaching deep
into our souls and grasping something
there that is so incredibly human
that it's hard to explain
but i do know that it's a beautiful
feeling sometimes tinged with fear and
an awareness that you're losing so much
of what you love
but you're also most certainly alive to
experience it
it's fascinating and yet frightening
i give thanks that i'm here in this town
because i'm able to help others get
through it and to practice love with
even more conviction that it's crucial
during times like these
during all times
[Music]
do
today was no different
my valley is in distress and i needed
something to take my mind off things
several new friends and i spent some
time walking through town sharing drinks
and discussing the incredible dedication
of our local smoke jumpers and
firefighters
it's so incredible to see people risking
their lives to save our home no more
than a speck on a map
[Music]
of course despite everything going on we
need to attempt to at least lead our
lives as we always have
it makes no sense to sit on our porches
and worry so when the winds changed and
took away the smoke for one blessed
morning we still hosted our farmers
market in hopes of cheering up anyone
who needed it
it was so wonderful to connect and share
smiles and laughs to exchange stories of
happier times knowing they will come
again
maybe it's a beautiful day after all
of course i don't want to focus on these
things too much so for the next several
weeks i won't dwell anymore on the fires
because life needs to continue and i
will treasure every minute of it
whoever you are and whatever type of day
you've had be it good or difficult or
somewhere in between i hope you never
forget to give and receive as much love
as possible
because this week i've realized more
than ever how important that is
our material possessions our
achievements even our very lives are
fleeting and can disappear right now
i have a whole new value for what it
means to be truly safe
in the face of a monster of fire eating
up my valley i see now that i will never
take my safety for granted again and i
hope you don't either
[Music]
oh thank you so much
you're welcome
[Music]
if you wish to take action to protect
our lands as usual i will leave links
below
making changes in our own lives to help
the environment is valuable but
pressuring larger companies and
organizations to have a change of heart
is even more crucial for the future if
you're falling asleep i'm sending you
dreams full of sunshine and blue skies
and clear air and most of all my love
take care
you